Arcee, a vehicular form is approaching.
阿尔茜 有车辆接近
Decepticon?
霸天虎吗？
Huh... Mom...
是我妈…
Again?
又来了？
She worries.
她担心我
Hi, honey.
嗨 甜心
Hey, eh...
嘿 呃…
Finished my shift early at the hospital, so I thought I'd swing by.
医院提前下班 所以我想顺便来看看
Good to see you again, doctor.
很高兴再见到你 医生
Arcee.
阿尔茜
So, where is Optimus?
对了 擎天柱在哪儿？
On a scouting mission with Bumblebee.
跟大黄蜂一起执行巡逻任务
Sorry to disappoint.
对不起让你扑空了
And I wore heels and everything...
我难得穿一次高跟鞋…
Mom!
妈妈！
That's odd.
真奇怪
This is an extremely unusual magnetic flux... for any planet.
这种磁通量在任何一个星球上都…极其罕见
I recognize this magnetic signature, Soundwave.
我认识这种磁力特征 声波
And it would be unfortunate to have a Decepticon invention such as this used against us.
这项霸天虎的发明要是落入敌手 可就太不幸了
I will secure the weapon, Lord Megatron.
我会取回这件武器 威震天陛下
Breakdown? Hah!
打击？哈！
If you can be bested by mere humans, what chance do you have against the Autobots?
你连区区人类都敌不过 还想对抗汽车人？
Allow me to redeem myself, master.
请允许我戴罪立功 主人
What I have lost is a constant reminder that I must never again fail you.
我所受到的羞辱 时刻提醒着我 决不再辜负您
Bulkhead's an animal!
隔板开车太猛了！
Remember when this used to be a secret club house?
我记得 这里是个秘密俱乐部吧？
Eh, don't worry, Miss Darby. We were wearing seatbelts.
呃 别担心 达比小姐 我们系了安全带
I'm sure you were, Rafael.
我相信你 拉斐尔
Hi, Miko! How's school going?
嗨 神子！学校里怎么样？
Why? What you hear?
什么？你听说什么了？
Let's do this thing, Jack.
我们得干活了 杰克
But, I just got here. I brought sandwiches.
可是 我刚到 我带了三明治喔
Mom. Look, I really need to help Arcee test her upgraded tracking system.
妈妈 我真得去帮阿尔茜 测试升级后的追踪系统
Well, just be careful.
好吧 只是 要小心
There's nothing to be careful about. It's a routine diagnostic.
没什么可小心的 只不过是例行检查
Are you sure you need Jack for that?
你非得让杰克帮忙吗？
Eh-oh...
啊哦
Bulkhead, I need you back in the field to investigate an odd magnetic disturbance.
隔板 你得再出趟外勤 调查一个诡异的磁力扰动
I'll go with!
我也要去！
Whoa, stay put, Miko.
喔 好好待着 神子
Why aren't you going with him?
你怎么不跟他去？
Someone thinks it's not safe.
某人觉得不安全
But it's safe for Jack to go with Arcee?
那杰克跟着阿尔茜就安全了？
Mom, totally different.
妈妈 这完全是两码事
Oh, how?
噢 说来听听
Mother knows best, Jack.
妈妈是为你好 杰克
Wait up, Bulkhead. I'm going with.
等等 隔板 我跟你去
Ah, what did I say?
啊 我说什么来着？
Jackpot.
中奖了
For me, you shouldn't have...
我觉得 你不该独吞…
I didn't.
我没有
I heard a rumour about a rogue 'Con.
我听说虎子出了个败类
How about I hogtie you and haul you in?
要不要我把你五花大绑 捉拿归案？
Huh, the primitive type.
哼 头脑简单 四肢发达
Not much for depth perception any more, are you?
独眼龙看不清目标距离 是吗？
Or not much for looks anymore.
八角怪还有脸说别人！
It was a lovely burial.
葬礼真感人
Sorry, can't quite understand you.
不好意思 你说什么我听不清
Don't take it so personal, Arcee.
那不是针对你 阿尔茜
Jack's mother's just... protective.
杰克的母亲只是…有保护欲望
Well, I protected her son for months before she had a clue.
可她不知道 这几个月我一直在保护她儿子
Suddenly she wakes up to reality and...
等她恍然大悟之后…
I'm not enough.
又觉得我不够好
No kidding!
没错！
Can't we ban her from the base?
我们能不能拒绝她来基地？
Miko, how did you...
神子 你怎么…
Gonna need a bridge.
呼叫环陆桥
Wait, don't send me back to helicopter mom.
等等 别把我送回那个护仔老妈手里
It's just... I miss the way things were.
我只是…怀念以前的时光
Strike that, Ratchet.
取消呼叫 救护车
It's only recon. She's safe with us.
继续巡逻 还是让她跟着我们吧
S-weet!
太好了！
Crank up track 7, Bulk.
劲爆第七曲 小隔
Track 7?
什么第七曲？
Do you think that's a little loud for a recon?
你不觉得 这样巡逻太吵了吗？
A scout should be silent but deadly.
侦察兵应该能杀人于无形
What?
怎么？
Silent but deadly means something completely different on earth.
“杀人于无形”在地球上说的完全是另一回事
Bulk, let's get our recon on.
小隔 我们继续巡逻吧
I always take point.
一向都是我领头的
I know, but Miko likes to be at front so she can see.
我知道 可是神子喜欢打前哨 可以看风景
No matter where I turn, I'm the third wheel.
不管到哪儿 我都是电灯泡
Hmm... looks like Ratchet's magnetic flux is coming from...
嗯…看来救护车说的磁通量就来自…
Airachnid...
毒蜘蛛
And Breakdown.
还有打击
Both your arch enemies.
正好是你们俩的宿敌
And they're mashing it up.
他们在窝里斗
Over that.
为了抢那个
The source of the magnetic disturbance.
那就是磁力扰动的来源
Alright, what's the plan?
很好 有什么计划？
Miko, don't move. I mean it.
神子 别动 我是认真的
Arcee. And look, you brought a new partner for me to snuff.
阿尔茜 看呐 你带来一个新搭档让我开荤
That would be Bulkhead.
那是隔板
Who asked you?
谁问你了？
Launch me.
人间大炮
No, she's mine.
不 她是我的
- Watch out for ... - Got it.
- 小心那个… - 明白
Wow. They're really good together.
哇哦 他们俩是绝配
Ugh... Smack down for the scrap book.
嗯 照下来放进纪念册
Ah... Thank you.
啊…谢谢
Do you even know what that does?
你会用那东西吗？
It isn't a toy.
那可不是玩具！
Hey!
嘿！
What's going...
怎么回…
Hmhmhmm... What's this switch do?
哼哼…这个开关是干嘛的？
Megatron's gonna love this.
威震天一定喜欢这东西
Bulkhead!
隔板！
The Cons are getting away.
虎子们逃跑了
Hey, my phone!
嘿 我的手机！
It's stuck!
粘住了！
Where is Arcee?
阿尔茜呢？
Why don't you just marry her?
你干脆跟她结婚好了
I'm right behind you.
我就在你后面
Where?
哪儿？
Let's just say... she's got your back.
你应该…不用担心后院起火了
Scrap.
见鬼
Breakdown here. I'm gonna need a bridge...
我是打击 我需要传送…
You've been magnetized... together?
你们被磁力吸到了一起？
Uh... They're inseparable.
呃 他们亲密无间
And the device that did this is on its way to Megatron.
而且那个磁力装置就要被威震天拿到手了
A polarity gauntlet. A deceptively simple but diabolical creation.
极化拳套 一项看似简单实则恐怖的发明
Just tell me you can unhitch us, Ratchet.
你到底能不能把我们分开 救护车
It may simply be a residual magnetic charge, providing your current attraction.
从目前的引力状况来看 可能只是残余的…磁力作用
They are not attracted to each other.
他们俩不仅仅是吸引！
But I'm afraid retrieving the gauntlet is our surest bet for reversing its effect.
恐怕抵消这个作用的最佳方案 是夺回拳套
Once Megatron gets his hands on the gauntlet...
威震天一旦拿到了这个拳套…
He'll use it for a whole lot more than attaching notes and family photos to the fridge.
肯定不会只用它 在冰箱上贴便签和家庭照片
Jack? I'm not following.
杰克？我没听明白
Madam, we are forged of metal alloy.
女士 我们是用合金铸造的
If Megatron could repel us with a flick of the switch, we might never again have another shot at him.
如果威震天按动开关就能把我们击退 我们可能再也没机会打败他了
Instant force field.
瞬间力场
Worse yet, he might use it to meld us all into a scrap pile.
更不用说 他可以用那东西把我们压成一堆废铁
The good news is the gauntlet hasn't travelled far.
好消息是 那个拳套还没走远
I would strongly advise pursuit.
我强烈建议你们追上去
We can catch up fast on wheels.
四个轮子 很快就到了
Whoa, whoa, whoa! And snap me in half?
喔 喔 喔！你想把我折成两半吗？
Right...
哦 对…
S-weet!
太棒了！
I'll take point.
我来领头
Not this time, kid.
这次不行 小鬼
What? But you said...
什么？可是你说过…
That was recon. This is war.
当时是巡逻 现在是战斗
I'm not risking your well-being just so you can hit your daily adrenaline quota.
我不能用你的安全冒险 你今天的历险到此为止
Ratchet, Miko needs a bridge.
救护车 神子需要环陆桥
Coming up.
就来
Ugh! You think Jack's mom's bad? You sound just like her.
呃！杰克的妈妈就够烦人了 可你说话跟她一样！
Is that such a bad thing?
关心孩子有什么不对吗？
I'm gonna go for her.
我去接她
It fits!
很称手嘛！
You know, a girl can never have too many accessaries.
你知道 女孩总是嫌首饰不够多
You were a Decepticon once. We can bring the prize to Megatron together.
你也当过霸天虎 我们可以一起把礼物献给威震天
Go back to that boys' club? I struck out on my own because I don't like to share.
让我回到那个狼窝？我出来单干 是因为我不喜欢与人分享
This will provide the perfect repellent against 'Bots and 'Cons alike.
这东西正好能让轮子和虎子都离我远点儿
Never had eyes in the back of my head before,
我的后脑勺以前从没长过眼睛
or blasters to cover my rear.
现在连后背都有枪了
And you get a built-in shield.
你也有了坚强的后盾
Bulkhead, you don't really think I sound like June, do you?
隔板 你不会也觉得我很像琼吧？
Er...
呃…
She's over protective.
她是过度保护
I'm just... protective.
我只是…一般保护
Totally different...
完全不同…
The gauntlet's close.
接近拳套了
I assume Arcee isn't far behind.
我猜 阿尔茜随后就到
You might say that.
可以这么说
Blast your hands in the air and turn around.
把手举起来 转过身去
Whatever you say...
遵命…
Still up for a truce, muscles?
停火协议还有效吗 肌肉男？
Only because I hate Bulkhead more than I hate you.
我只不过是更恨隔板罢了
Oh... What?
噢…怎么？
Bulkhead, would you stay still?
隔板 你能站着别动吗？
My bad.
我的错
Whoa...
喔
Need a hand?
需要帮手吗？
No, she's mine!
不 她是我的！
Two Bots. One stump.
两个轮子 一起送命
Bulk, duck!
小隔 低头！
Bulkhead... Get... up!
隔板…起…来！
Pins like a bug.
骨瘦如柴
Of course I can think of one permanent way out of your predicament.
当然了 我有个一劳永逸的办法让你解脱
I'll take topside.
我攻上盘
Hah!
哈！
I'm free.
我自由了
Wanna dance?
想跳个舞吗？
You're not my type.
你不是我喜欢的类型
Scrap.
见鬼
Let's leave the boys to themselves.
让男生们自己玩吧
That would be the upclose and personal setting.
我们两个私下里谈谈
One hand tied, five more to play with.
一条腿废了 还有五条陪你玩儿
Quality, not quantity.
质量不过关 再多也没用
Opposite do not attract.
同性相斥
We can't touch metal.
我们碰不到金属物体
We are polarized.
我们被极化了
Always leave on the high note.
我总是见好就收
Bulkhead, the gauntlet!
隔板 拳套！
Let's finish this.
把他们解决掉吧
And risk becoming twins again?
不怕再次合体吗？
Souvenir, but...
是个纪念品 不过…
We don't advise indoor use.
不建议在室内使用
Eyu... They even finish each other's sentences.
哎哟 他们都开始一唱一和了
Miko, check it out-- new battle scars.
神子 看看这个――几道新伤
Arcee, hey...
阿尔茜 嘿…
Let the adults talk.
小孩子别插嘴
Arcee, I think I owe you an apology.
阿尔茜 我想我应该向你道歉
You do?
是吗？
I worry... especially when I feel like I can't control things--
我经常担心…尤其是觉得力不从心的时候
which, with a teenager, is all the time.
照顾一个处在青春期的孩子 太操心了
Jack and I have always been close.
杰克和我一直很亲近
Especially, after his dad left. And...
特别是他父亲离开之后…
I guess it's just... hard to accept that all that's changing.
我想我只是…很难一下子接受生活的变化
I mean I knew it would someday, but...
我也知道 生活迟早要改变 只是…
you're not quite the type of girl I thought Jack would be ditching me for.
你不是我想象的那种 让杰克鬼迷心窍的女孩
I think we've all been a little guilty of staying attached to the way things were.
我想我们都有点过于留恋从前的时光
Breakdown, you dare to return empty-handed?!
打击 你竟敢空手回来见我？！
No, Master.
不 主人
Airachnid... it has been some time.
毒蜘蛛…久违了
Lord Megatron... what can I say? It's good to be back.
威震天陛下…说什么好呢？很高兴能归队